<rss xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Zrodowatch Custom feed</title>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com</link>
<description>Zrodowatch Custom feed xml file</description>
<pubDate>2024-09-17T07:29:12Z</pubDate>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/audemars-piguet-royal-oak-extrathin-15202baoo1240ba02a?variant=66e8e51ee6662b9f1af141c3</link>
<g:item_group_id>AAA</g:item_group_id>
<description>At a price of only 1/10 of the Authentic one, you can own a handcrafted version with 99.99% precision of the Auth edition, complete with certification and a great warranty, and excellent customer service.&nbsp;CATEGORYWATCHESBRANDAUDEMARS PIGUETMODELROYAL OAK EXTRA-THINREF NO.15202BA.OO.1240BA.02.AGTC REFGTC-2053DIALCHAMPAGNE WITH GOLD RAISED AP ON 6 O'CLOCKGLASSSAPPHIRE CRYSTALMOVEMENTSELFWINDING CALIBRE 2121FUNCTIONSHOURS, MINUTES, DATECASEYELLOW GOLDDIAMETER39MMWATERPROOF50MBRACELETYELLOW GOLDBUCKLEHIDDEN FOLDING CLASPYEAR2019ADDITIONAL INFOORIGINAL BOX AND PAPERS&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Audemars Piguet Royal Oak Extra-Thin 15202BA.OO.1240BA.02.A</title>
<g:price>369.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>100</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff46d513c5272425cd1d6.jpg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/audemars-piguet-royal-oak-15510orood315cr02-selfwinding-rose-gold-blue-dial-2023?variant=66e8e51de6662b9f1af1415c</link>
<g:item_group_id>BBB</g:item_group_id>
<description>This Royal Oak Selfwinding is designed in a 41mm 18k rose gold case with a smooth octagonal bezel, glareproofed sapphire crystal and caseback, screw-locked crown. It features a blue 'Grande Tapisserie' pattern on the dial and is complimented by a blue alligator strap with 18k rose gold AP folding clasp.&nbsp;Reference Number15510OR.OO.D315CR.02ModelRoyal Oak SelfwindingMovementAutomaticCase MaterialRose GoldBracelet MaterialBlue Alligator Leather &nbsp;DialBlue &nbsp;Case Diameter41mmYear2023ConditionNewBox &amp; PapersOriginal box, original papersIndulge in the epitome of luxury and sophistication with the Audemars Piguet Royal Oak Selfwinding 41mm Rose Gold Blue Dial 15510OR.OO.D315CR.02. This exquisite timepiece from the iconic Royal Oak collection exudes timeless elegance and exceptional craftsmanship, making it a true statement of refined style.&nbsp; The 41mm case, meticulously crafted from lustrous rose gold, showcases the iconic octagonal shape that has become synonymous with Audemars Piguet. Its polished and satin-brushed finish adds depth and character to the design, while the integrated bracelet seamlessly blends with the case for a harmonious aesthetic.&nbsp; The captivating blue dial, adorned with the signature "Grande Tapisserie" pattern, is a mesmerizing canvas that catches the light from every angle. The rose gold hands and hour markers beautifully contrast against the deep blue backdrop, ensuring optimal legibility in any lighting condition.&nbsp; Powered by a self-winding movement, this timepiece offers precise and reliable timekeeping, while the date display at 3 o'clock adds practicality to its allure. With a water resistance of up to 50 meters, it is also built to withstand the rigors of everyday life.&nbsp; The Audemars Piguet Royal Oak Selfwinding 41mm Rose Gold Blue Dial 15510OR.OO.D315CR.02 represents the perfect blend of classic design and contemporary aesthetics. It is a testament to the brand's unwavering commitment to exceptional quality...</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Audemars Piguet Royal Oak 15510OR.OO.D315CR.02 Selfwinding Rose Gold Blue Dial (2023)</title>
<g:price>339.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>101</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff46b513c5272425cd11f.jpg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/rolex-datejust-36-blue-roman-numeral-dial-116234-ar-luxury-1?variant=66e8e51de6662b9f1af140d7</link>
<g:item_group_id>CCC</g:item_group_id>
<description>At a price of only 1/10 of the Authentic one, you can own a handcrafted version with 99.99% precision of the Auth edition, complete with certification and a great warranty, and excellent customer service.*** With many years of experience in luxury watches and jewelry, our team of experienced and well-trained staff will bring you the most prestigious products.Swiss-made movements with 99.99% precision from the most minor details- 5-year movement warranty- Easy payment support via Paypal, Stripe, etcProduct DetailsBasic InfoBrandRolexModelDatejust 41Reference number126334 &nbsp;MovementAutomaticCase materialSteelBracelet materialSteelYear of production2021GenderMen's watch/UnisexCaliberMovementAutomaticCaliber/movement3235Base caliberRolex 3135Power reserve70 hNumber of jewels31CaseCase materialSteelCase diameter41 mmWater resistance10 ATMBezel materialWhite goldCrystalSapphire crystalDialBlueDial numeralsRoman numeralsBracelet/strapBracelet materialSteelBracelet colorSteelClaspFold claspClasp materialSteel&nbsp;</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Rolex Datejust 41 Blue Roman Numeral Dial Men's Watch 126334-0026</title>
<g:price>319.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>103</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff46b513c5272425cd086.jpg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/patek-philippe-nautilus-57121a001-stainless-steel?variant=66e8e51ce6662b9f1af14051</link>
<g:item_group_id>AAA</g:item_group_id>
<description>Model&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nautilus Model Number&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;5712/1A-001 Year&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;2014 Movement&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;mechanical-automatic Original Box&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yes Original Papers&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yes Gender&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;mens Diameter (mm)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;40 Watch Case Material&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;stainless-steel Watch Band Material&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;stainless-steel Warranty&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;12Months Returns&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;14 Days Money Back Guarantee Product Code&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;05726This pre-owned stainless steel Patek Philippe Nautilus ref. 5712/1A-001 really shows off the true meaning of sophisticated elegance featuring a 40mm case, blue dial with moonphase, power reserve, date &amp; seconds sub dial display on a stainless steel bracelet with a hidden folded clasp. Sophisticated as it can be, Patek Philippe wanted to show not only their aesthetics but also their master engineering through a sapphire crystal glass back showing you the calibre 240 PS IRM C LU automatic winding movement with approximately 48 hours power reserve. As you can see in the pictures, the watch is like new in absolute mint condition and comes complete with the original Patek Philippe box &amp; papers. As you can see we are asking more than the retail price on this watch as its under very high demand and production is very low. You would expect to wait a few years before you can get your hands on one from the Patek Philippe boutique. This watch receives our personal recommendations for quality, investment value, functionality, pure elegance. We guarantee that this watch has been tested thoroughly for time accuracy, functionality and has been serviced to the highest standards according to the manufacturers specification. We have also performed a very precise condition check to determine the level of refurbishment required to meet our high standards of quality. This watch has also been checked...</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Patek Philippe Nautilus 5712-1A-001 Stainless Steel</title>
<g:price>359.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>104</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff469513c5272425ccfdb.jpeg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/patek-philippe-nautilus-5980r-flyback-chronograph-date-rose-gold-leather-strap?variant=66e8e51ce6662b9f1af13fcc</link>
<g:item_group_id>BBB</g:item_group_id>
<description>Basic InfoListing codeF4GPO0BrandPatek PhilippeModelNautilusReference number5980R-001 &nbsp;Dealer product code0057MovementAutomaticCase materialRose goldYear of production2022 (Approximation)&nbsp;&nbsp;Scope of deliveryOriginal box, original papersGenderMen's watch/UnisexLocationUnited States of America, New York, New YorkPrice$132,000AvailabilityItem is in stockCaliberMovementAutomaticCaliber/movementCH 28-520 CPower reserve55 hNumber of jewels35CaseCase materialRose goldCase diameter40.5 mm Try it onWater resistance10 ATMBezel materialRose goldCrystalSapphire crystalDialBrownDial numeralsNo numeralsBracelet/strapBracelet colorBrownClaspFold claspClasp materialRose GoldFunctionsChronograph, DateReference: 5980R-001 Year: 2022 Material: Rose Gold Case Diameter: 40.5mm Dial: Black-Brown Glass: Sapphire Condition: Unworn Comes with Original Box And Original Papers With the rounded octagonal shape of its bezel, the ingenious porthole construction of its case, and its horizontally embossed dial, the Nautilus has epitomized the elegant sports watch since 1976. Forty years later, it comprises a splendid collection of models for men and women. In steel, rose gold, white gold or two-tone combinations they accompany the most active lifestyles with incomparable class. Mechanical self-winding movement with date. Caliber CH 28520 C. Flyback chronograph. Black brown, gold applied hour markers with luminescent coating. Rose gold. Screw-down crown. Sapphire-crystal case back. Water-resistant to 120m. Case diameter (10-4 o'clock): 40.5 mm. Height: 12.2 mm. Alligator strap with rectangular scales, hand-stitched, matt dark brown. Nautilus fold-over clasp</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Patek Philippe Nautilus 5980R Flyback Chronograph Date Rose Gold Leather Strap</title>
<g:price>359.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>105</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff469513c5272425ccf7f.jpeg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/audemars-piguet-royal-oak-chronograph-white-dial-rose-gold-on-904l-steel?variant=66e8e51be6662b9f1af13efc</link>
<g:item_group_id>CCC</g:item_group_id>
<description>REF. #26320OR.OO.1220OR.02 Genuine Swiss 7750 Movement re-aligned to resemble the 3126 Audemars Piguet Movement with Functional stopwatch feature like the authentic White Grande Tapisserie dial with 3 Silver Functional Sub Dials and Date Window. 904L Steel Case with 10.0 Microns Thick Rose Gold Plating Complete with AP MArkings and Engravings. Scratch Proof Sapphire Crystals with Correct Date Cyclops and Double AR Coating 904L Stainless Steel Strap with 10 Microns Thick Rose Gold Plating complete with AP Deployant Clasps with all markings exactly as per the Genuine 41MM in Diameter x 16MM Thick Solid Case back with Sapphire Crystals complete with AP markings and Engravings Exact Weight and Dimensions to the Authentic Watches Water Resistant and Waterproof up to 50 Meters&nbsp;</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Audemars Piguet Royal Oak Chronograph White Dial Rose Gold on 904L Steel</title>
<g:price>359.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>106</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff468513c5272425ccef6.jpeg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/patek-philippe-nautilus-ladies-automatic-watch-18k-rose-gold-352mm-ref-71181r001?variant=66e8e51ae6662b9f1af13de5</link>
<g:item_group_id>AAA</g:item_group_id>
<description>SpecificationsMakePatek PhilippeModelNautilusReference7118/1R-001Diameter35,2mmCase Material18k Rose GoldDial ColorSilvery OpalineBezel TypeFixedBezel ColorPinkBezel Material18k Rose GoldCrystalScratch Resistant Sapphire crystalMovementSelf-winding mechanicalBracelet TypeBraceletBracelet Material18k Rose GoldClasp18k Rose Gold Nautilus fold-over claspFunctionsDate in an aperture, Hour, Minute, Sweep seconds handWater ResistanceUp to 60m/200ft (6 ATM)WarrantyBalance of Covered with Patek Philippe 2-Year International WarrantyLadies Watch Patek Philippe Nautilus 18k Rose Gold case with polished and satin finishes, 35,2mm, Reference 7118/1R-001 - has been the standard in luxury, because combine elegance, sporty style and timeless design. Is striking watch boasts a Silvery Opaline with horizontally embossed dial, 18k Rose Gold applied hour markers and Arabic numeral at the 12 o'clock positioning with a luminescent coating for easy readability in dim lighting as well as Dot minute markers around the outer rim. The sweep seconds hand and date in an aperture features at the 6 o'clock positioning give this model a clean profile and make keeping track of both date and time convenient. Complementing the elegant dial are 18k Rose Gold polished luminous alpha-style shape hands. A polished 18k Rose Gold Screw-down crown with a ribbed edge for easy grip and the Patek Philippe logo is completes the watch's harmony. The dial closed by a Scratch-resistant Sapphire Crystal. Sapphire-crystal too case back, which allows of the case, allows you to see the magical work of the movement. The wide hexagonal with polished and satin finishes bezel, in a blushing 18k Rose Gold, provides a wide view of the dial as the horizon is visible through the porthole. Moreover, the side protrusions, also called "lugs", are inspired by the hinges on these windows. The Model has caliber Patek Philippe Caliber 324 S C, with a self-winding mechanical movement containing 29 Jewels, with a power reserve of...</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Patek Philippe Nautilus Ladies Automatic Watch, 18k Rose Gold, 35,2mm, Ref# 7118/1R-001</title>
<g:price>359.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>107</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff467513c5272425cce7f.jpg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/panerai-luminor-1950-3-days-gmt-automatic-ceramica-44mm-black-dial-mens-watch-pam00441?variant=66e8e519e6662b9f1af13cb8</link>
<g:item_group_id>BBB</g:item_group_id>
<description>Item No PN062 -Panerai Box &amp; Warranty Card BRAND Panerai MODEL Luminor 1950 Pam00441 SERIAL/YEAR Current CASE DIAMETER 44mm DIAL Black Under certain circumstances, an advertised item may be out of stock. DESCRIPTION Home Panerai Luminor 1950 3 Days Gmt Automatic Ceramica 44mm Black Dial Men's Watch Pam00441 Titanium case with a brown leather strap. Titanium bezel. Brown dial with index-Arabic numerals hour markers. Dial Type: Analog. Luminescent hands and markers. Date display at the 3 o'clock position. One- small seconds subdials. Panerai Calibre P.9010 automatic movement with a 3-day power reserve. Scratch resistant sapphire crystal. Case size: 44 mm. Cushion case shape. Water resistant at 30 meters / 100 feet. Functions: date, hour, minute, second. Luxury watch style. Watch label: Swiss Made. Panerai Luminor Marina 1950 Brown Dial Automatic Mens Brown Leather Watch PAM01351</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Panerai Luminor 1950 3 Days Gmt Automatic Ceramica 44mm Black Dial Men's Watch Pam00441</title>
<g:price>339.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>108</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666ff46c513c5272425cd197.png</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/like-new-complete-local-nov-18-panerai-luminor-due-45-gmt-sports-grey-3-days-pam-944-pam944?variant=66e8e517e6662b9f1af13ad6</link>
<g:item_group_id>CCC</g:item_group_id>
<description>DetailsBrandPaneraiGenderUnisexThe Panerai PAM944 is a watch model from the Panerai brand and Luminor collection. As of April 2024, the average price of the Panerai Luminor Due 45 3 Days GMT Power Reserve Automatic (PAM944)</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Panerai Luminor Due 45 GMT Sports Grey 3 Days Pam 944</title>
<g:price>349.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>109</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666fef90513c5272425c5d5c.png</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/cartier-santos-de-cartier-large-smoky-green-dial-automatic-braceletstrap-watch?variant=66e8e516e6662b9f1af13a06</link>
<g:item_group_id>AAA</g:item_group_id>
<description>BRANDCartierCASE DIAMETER47.5mm x 39.8mmCOLLECTIONSantosDIAL COLOURGreenGENDERMensGUARANTEE2 Years (Register online for 8 YearsMATERIALSteelMOVEMENTAutomaticPRODUCT CODEWSSA0062STRAP TYPEBracelet/Strap</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Cartier Santos de Cartier Large Smoky Green Dial Automatic Bracelet/Strap Watch</title>
<g:price>339.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>110</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666fef90513c5272425c5d4c.png</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/rolex-daydate-40-40mm-chocolate-baguette-dial-rose-gold-bracelet-2023?variant=66e8e515e6662b9f1af138f7</link>
<g:item_group_id>BBB</g:item_group_id>
<description>Basic InfoListing codeCZ81U3BrandRolexModelDay-Date 40Reference number228235-0006 &nbsp;MovementAutomaticCase materialRose goldBracelet materialRose goldYear of production2023ConditionUnworn (Mint condition, without signs of wear)Scope of deliveryOriginal box, original papersGenderMen's watch/UnisexLocationUnited States of America, New York, New YorkPrice&nbsp;AvailabilityItem is in stockCaliberMovementAutomaticCaliber/movement3255Power reserve70 hNumber of jewels31CaseCase materialRose goldCase diameter40 mm Try it onWater resistance10 ATMBezel materialRose goldCrystalSapphire crystalDialBrownBracelet/strapBracelet materialRose goldBracelet colorGoldClasp materialRose GoldFunctionsWeekday</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Rolex Day-Date 40mm Chocolate Baguette Dial Rose Gold Bracelet 2023</title>
<g:price>339.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>111</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666fef8f513c5272425c5d19.jpg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/panerai-pam-1342-luminor-luna-rossa-44mm?variant=66e8e513e6662b9f1af136ad</link>
<g:item_group_id>CCC</g:item_group_id>
<description>GENERALModelPAM 1342MovementManual WindEngineP. 6000Power Reserve72GenderGentlemenCASECase Size44mmMaterialStainless SteelCase BackSolidBezelStainless SteelCrownStainless SteelDIALDial ColorWhiteLuminescenceYesCONDITIONConditionExcellentBRACELETBracelet MaterialBlack Rubber with Textile InlayFEATURESComplicationsManual WindWater Resistance100m / 330ftPACKAGINGBoxYesBookletIncludedWarranty Papers / CardYes</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Panerai PAM 1342 Luminor Luna Rossa 44mm</title>
<g:price>339.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>112</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666fef8e513c5272425c5cda.jpeg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/rolex-sky-dweller-42mm-mens-watch?variant=66e8e511e6662b9f1af133fb</link>
<g:item_group_id>AAA</g:item_group_id>
<description>Case ShapeRoundCase Dimensions42mmCase MaterialStainless SteelDial ColorWhiteCrystalScratch Resistant SapphireBezelBi-Directional RotatingScrew-in CrownYesWater Resistance100m/330ftCase BackSolidBand MaterialStainless SteelColor/FinishBrushed &amp; PolishedBand NameRolex JubileeClaspRolex Folding OysterclaspClasp FeaturesEasylink 5mm comfort extension linkMovementAutomaticComplicationsAnnual Calendar, GMT Time Zone</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Rolex Sky Dweller 42mm Mens Watch</title>
<g:price>329.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>113</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666fef8c513c5272425c5c6d.jpeg</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/panerai-submersible-quarantaquattro-bianco-pam01226--white-dial-44mm?variant=66e8e50ee6662b9f1af130d1</link>
<g:item_group_id>BBB</g:item_group_id>
<description>DescriptionThe 44mm PAM 01226 Submersible Bianco is an absolute masterpiece within the Panerai lineup. This refreshing timepiece boasts a reliable, automatic P.900 movement. Its textured white dial with incredible lume and crisp, black elements is both legible and aesthetically pleasing. This versatile Panerai will be a fantastic addition to any man's collection.Basic InfoListing codeI4YNQ4BrandPaneraiModelLuminor SubmersibleReference numberPAM 01226 &nbsp;MovementAutomaticCase materialSteelBracelet materialRubberYear of production2023ConditionnewScope of deliveryOriginal box, original papersGenderMen's watch/UnisexLocationUnited States of America, Wisconsin, JEFFERSON&nbsp;&nbsp;AvailabilityItem is in stockCaliberMovementAutomaticCaliber/movementP.900Power reserve72 hCaseCase materialSteelCase diameter44 mm Try it onWater resistance30 ATMBezel materialSteelCrystalSapphire crystalDialWhiteDial numeralsNo numeralsBracelet/strapBracelet materialRubberBracelet colorGreenClaspBuckleClasp materialSteel</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Panerai Submersible QuarantaQuattro Bianco PAM01226 – White Dial 44mm</title>
<g:price>369.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>114</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666fef8d513c5272425c5ca9.webp</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
<item>
<g:gender>unisex</g:gender>
<link>https://zrodowatch.com/products/breitling-navitimer-world-a24322-hh10flashdeal?variant=66e8e50ce6662b9f1af12f07</link>
<g:item_group_id>CCC</g:item_group_id>
<description>You can own a handcrafted version with 99.99% precision of the Auth edition, complete with certification and a great warranty, and excellent customer service. *** With many years of experience in luxury watches and jewelry, our team of experienced and well-trained staff will bring you the most prestigious products. - Swiss-made movements with 99.99% precision from the most minor details - 5-year movement warranty - Easy payment support via Paypal, Stripe, etc Brand Breitling Range Navitimer World Model A24322 Gender Mens Movement Automatic Case_size 46 MM Case_material Steel Bracelet_material Steel (Navitimer) Dial_type White Baton Water_resistance Water Resistant &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;</description>
<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
<title>Breitling Navitimer World A24322</title>
<g:price>313.99 USD</g:price>
<g:id>115</g:id>
<g:google_product_category>201</g:google_product_category>
<g:image_link>https://minio.cacheimg.com/img/720/0/resize/65dc3392655c5b0009ec8416/2024/06/17/product-img-666fef8d513c5272425c5c93.png</g:image_link>
<g:age_group>adult</g:age_group>
<g:identifier_exists>false</g:identifier_exists>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<g:product_type>Watch</g:product_type>
<g:shipping_weight>1</g:shipping_weight>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
